https://www.birthdaydirect.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
BirthdayDirect.com carefully protects the privacy of your information submitted via the Internet or otherwise, and does not sell or pass on your name or personal information without your express permission.
Any personal information that you share with us and with the business partners that help this site function or assist us in fulfilling your order, is kept absolutely private. Neither your name nor anything about you is sold or shared with any other non-affiliated company or agency. In order to ship and track merchandise, we make your name and address available to companies such as the United States Postal Service and Federal Express. In no instances are these business affiliates allowed to use your personal information for any other purpose aside from shipping.
My account - You have the opportunity to create a personal shopping account with Birthday Direct, Inc. This account will allow you to shop faster and easier and to check on order status and history. In creating this account, you authorize Birthday Direct, Inc., to store your name, e-mail address, telephone number, shipping and billing addresses. This is for your convenience only. The information is not used for any other purpose.
Mailing List - When you create an account with Birthday Direct, Inc., you will be given the option to be added to the Birthday Direct, Inc., mailing list. Whether or not you select this option, your personal information will never be shared with or sold to anyone. Additionally, subscriptions to the mailing list can be cancelled at any time.
Purchases - When you place an order, you will be asked to provide your credit card information. Birthday Direct, Inc., does not, however, store your credit card information.
Cookies - The cookie holds information a site may need to personalize/enhance your experience and to gather website statistical data, such as which pages are visited, the internet provider's domain name and the addresses of the sites visited immediately before coming to and immediately after leaving www.birthdaydirect.com. However, none of this information is associated with you as an individual. It is measured anonymously and only in the aggregate. Cookies contain absolutely no personal information. You may disable cookies on your browser. Please review your browser's instructions for doing so.
Consent - You acknowledge that this privacy policy is part of the terms and service, and you agree that using this site signifies your assent to the Birthday Direct, Inc., Privacy Policy. Birthday Direct, Inc.,reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without advanced notice. If the Birthday Direct, Inc., Privacy Policy is changed, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information is collected, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Children's Online Privacy - This Website is not marketed to, and does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected or received personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have received any information from a child under the age of 13, please let us know.
×
OK
